Guide to the ILR School Communications Department Publications 1996-2018
ILR School Communications Department Publications
- ILR Communications Department Publications, 2000-2004 (Box 1)
  - Professional Development Workshops and Certificates Catalog, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Item 1: Professional Development Workshops and Certificates, Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - HR and EEO Complaint Handling Workshops and Certificates Catalog, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Item 1: HR and EEO Complaint Handling, Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Item 2: HR and EEO Complaint Handling, Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Item 3: HR and EEO Complaint Handling, Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Change Management Workshops, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Item 1: Change Management Workshops Held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Item 2: Change Management Workshops Held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Item 3: Change Management Workshops Held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Human Resources Workshops, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Item 1: Human Resources Professional Development Workshops Held in New York City and Long Island, Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Item 2: Human Resources Professional Development Workshops Held in New York City and Long Island, Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Item 3: Human Resources Professional Development Workshops Held in New York City and Long Island, Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Item 4: Human Resources Professional Development Workshops Held in Long Island, New York, Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Item 5: Human Resources Professional Development Workshops Held in Long Island, New York, Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Item 6: Human Resources Workshops Held in Rochester, New York, Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Item 7: Human Resources Workshops Held in Rochester, New York, Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Item 8: Human Resources Workshops Held in Rochester, New York, Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Professional Development Workshops, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Item 1: Professional Development Workshops Held in Albany, New York, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Item 2: Professional Development Workshops Held in Albany, New York, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Item 3: Professional Development Workshops Held in Albany, New York, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Item 4: Professional Development Workshops Held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Item 5: Professional Development Workshops Held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Item 6: Professional Development Workshops Held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Item 7: Professional Development Workshops Held in Ithaca, NY, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Item 8: Professional Development Workshops Held in Ithaca, NY, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Labor Relations Workshops, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Item 1: Labor Relations Professional Development Workshops Held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Item 2: Labor Relations Professional Development Workshops Held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Item 3: Labor Relations Professional Development Workshops Held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Item 4: Labor Relations Workshops Held at Cornell Universitys Workplace Education Center in Buffalo, NY, Publication (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Item 5: Labor Relations Workshops Held at Cornell Universitys Workplace Education Center in Buffalo, NY, Publication (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Item 6: Labor Relations Workshops Held at Cornell Universitys Workplace Education Center in Buffalo, NY, Publication (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Labor Studies Certificate Program, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Item 1: Labor Studies Certificate Program Held in Rochester, New York, Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Item 2: Labor Studies Certificate Program Held evenings in Cheektowaga, New York, Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Dispute Management Workshops, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Item 1: Diversity Management Professional Development Workshops held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Item 2: Diversity Management Professional Development Workshops held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Item 3: Diversity Management Professional Development Workshops held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Equal Employment Opportunities Workshop, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Item 1: Equal Employment Opportunities Professional Development Workshops held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Item 2: Equal Employment Opportunities Professional Development Workshops held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Item 3: Equal Employment Opportunities Professional Development Workshops held in New York City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Management and Professional Development Workshops, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Item 1: Management and Professional Development Workshops, Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Item 2: Management and Professional Development Workshops, Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Item 3: Management and Professional Development Workshops, Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Management Development Workshops, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Item 1: Management and Professional Development Workshops held in New York City and Long Island, Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Item 2: Management and Professional Development Workshops held in New York City and Long Island, Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Item 3: Management and Professional Development Workshops held in New York City and Long Island, Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Item 4: Management and Professional Development Workshops held in Long Island, New York, Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Item 5: Management and Professional Development Workshops held in Long Island, New York, Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Item 6: Management and Professional Development Workshops held in Long Island, New York, Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Management Development and Human Resources Workshops, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Item 1: Workshops in Management Development and Human Resources, Publication (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Item 2: Workshops in Management Development and Human Resources, Publication (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Item 3: Workshops in Management Development and Human Resources, Publication (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Labor Relations and EEO Workshops, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Item 1: Labor Relations and EEO Workshops Professional Development Training in Buffalo, New York, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Item 2: Labor Relations and EEO Workshops Professional Development Training in Buffalo, New York, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Graduate Programs in Industrial and Labor Relations, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Item 1: Become a Leader in the Workplace, Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - ILR Connections, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Item 1: ILR Connections, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - IWS Briefing, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Item 1: Institute for Workplace Studies, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - ILR Celebration, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    October 15th-16th
    - Item 1: You're Invited to an ILR Celebration, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Item 2: You're Invited to an ILR Celebration, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Item 3: You're Invited to an ILR Celebration, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Item 4: Show: Communication and marketing Services, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Item 5: Upstate Union Workshop Series, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Miscellaneous Brochures, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Item 1: Show: Communication and Marketing Services, Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Item 2: Upstate Union Workshop Series, Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Item 3: Anheuser-Busch Professional Development Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
      By Cornell University School of Hotel Administration. Item is in English.
    - Item 4: The Spring 2004 Workplace Colloquium Series, Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
- ILR Communications Department Publications, 2004-2013; Undated, Publication (Box 2)
  - Change Management Workshops, 2004-2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Diversity Management Workshops, 2004-2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - EEO Workshops, 2004-2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Human Resources Workshops, 2004-2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Labor Relations Workshops, 2004-2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Leadership Development Workshops, 2004-2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Management Development and Human Resources Workshop, 2004-2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Management Studies in Western New York, 2004-2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Supervisory and Management Workshops, 2004-2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Cornell Labor Programs: Upstate Union Workshops, 2004-2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - ILR Executive Education Programs, 2004-2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Professional Development Workshops and Certificate Catalog, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Management and Professional Development, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Professional Development Workshops, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Human Resources Workshops, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - EEO Workshops, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Diversity Management Workshops, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Labor Relations Workshops, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Management and Professional Development Workshops, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Professional Development Catalog, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Management and Professional Development Workshops, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Fall 2005 Workshops, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - High Performance Change, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Labor Studies Certificate Program, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Winter
  - Martin P. Catherwood Library, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - IWS Briefing, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Human Resources Workshops, 2005-2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - ILR Catalog, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Diversity, Inclusion, and EEO Programs, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Professional Development Workshops, 2006; Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - The Program on Conflict Resolution, 2006-2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Workshop Brochures, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - A Personal Invitation to Meet with ILR Alumni, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - ILR Catalog, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - The ILR School, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Can Buffalo Take the High Road Out of Poverty?, 2007; Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Diversity, Inclusion, and EEO Practice, 2007-2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Labor Relations Program, 2007-2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Human Resources Program, 2007-2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - ILR Catalog, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Workshop Brochures, 2008; Publication (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - ILR Catalog, 2008-2009; Publication (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Workshop Brochures, 2008-2009; Publication (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - ILR Catalog, 2009; Publication (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Workshop Brochures, 2009; Publication (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Workshop Brochures, 2009-2010; Publication (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Workshop Brochures, Publication (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Labor's Future Starts Today, 2010; Publication (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - ILR Our People, Our Mission, Our Spirit, 2010; Publication (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - A Guide to Advancing Your Career, Your Workplace, 2010; Publication (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - A Personal Invitation to Meet with ILR Alumni, 2010; Publication (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - ILR Postgraduate Reports, 2010; Publication (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Milton Konvitz Memorial Lecture Poster, 2010; Publication (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - You Can Get There From Here, 2010-2011; Publication (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Workshop Brochures, 2010-2011; Publication (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Certificate in Management Workshops, 2010-2011; Publication (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Institute for Compensation Studies, 2011; Publication (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Ph.D. in Human Resource Management, 2011; Publication (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Will You be a Leader in Tomorrow's World of Work, 2011; Publication (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - ILR Postgraduate Report, Publication (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Groat and Alpern Awards, 2011; Publication (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Workshops, Certificates, and Customized Programs, 2011-2012; Publication (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Human Capital Development Workshops and Certificate Programs, 2012; Publication (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Human Resource Management Certificate, 2012; Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - ILR Postgraduate Report, Publication (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Groat and Alpern Awards, 2012; Publication (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Advance: ILR Alumni Magazine, 2012; Publication (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Milton Konvitz Memorial Lecture Poster, 2012; Publication (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - ILR Review, 2012; Publication (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Public Engagement, 2012; Publication (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Human Capital Development, 2012-2013; Publication (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Human Capital Development, 2013; Publication (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - The Scheinman Institute on Conflict Resolution, 2013; Publication (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Groat and Alpern Awards, 2013; Publication (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Advance: ILR Alumni Magazine, 2013; Publication (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Information Packet, 2013; Publication (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Management Programs and Workshops, 1997-1998; Publication (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - This Is Cornell, 2002; Publication (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - The Kheel Center, 2005; Publication (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Catherwood Library, Publication (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Cornell ILR Management Studies, Publication (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Cornell Labor Studies, Publication (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - A Guide to Workplace Resources, Publication (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - ILR Phase II Construction Project, Publication (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Interest Based Bargaining, Publication (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Labor Relations Programs, Publication (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Labor Studies Classes Online, Publication (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Labor and Complaint Handling Programs, Publication (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - A New Approach to Advancing Your Career, Publication (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - On-Site Workshops, Publication (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Preventing and Managing Crisis in Your Workplace, Publication (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Union Leadership, Publication (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Working Together, Publication (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Workplace Health and Safety, Publication (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - You're Invited, Publication (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Advance: ILR Alumni Magazine, 2013; Publication (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Earn A Master's Degree at Cornell, In New York City, 2013; Publication (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Accelerate Your Career, 2014; Publication (Box 2, Folder 98)
- Other ILR-Related Cornell Publications, 1996-2013; Undated; Communications, 2014-, Publication (Box 3)
  - 50 Years: 50 (or so) Fascinating Alumni, 1996; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: 50 (or so) Fascinating Alumni, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
      By Cornell Univeristy ILR School. Item is in English.
  - ILR Floral Education, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: Global Education, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
      By Cornell University ILR School. Item is in English.
  - ILR Connections, 2006; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: Advancing the World of Work Celebrating Outreach, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Celebrate 60!, 2007; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: Celebrate 60!, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - International at ILR, 2009; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: Advancing the World of Work Globally, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The ILR School, 2010-2011; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: The ILR School, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Development Programs, 2011; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: Cornell Labor Arbitrator Development Program, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Item 2: Cornell Labor Arbitrator Development Program, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
      By Cornell University ILR School. copy 2. Item is in English.
    - Item 3: Cornell Labor Arbitrator Development Program, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
      By Cornell University ILR School. copy 3. Item is in English.
    - Item 4: Cornell Professional Neutral Development Program, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Item 5: Cornell Professional Neutral Development Program, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Item 6: Cornell Professional Neutral Development Program, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - ILR Credit Internship Program, 2011-2012; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: ILR Credit Internship Program, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - ILR/UCD Semester in Dublin Program, 2013; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: ILR/UCD Semester in Dublin Program, Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Item 2: ILR/UCD Semester in Dublin Program, Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Item 3: ILR/UCD Semester in Dublin Program, Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Far Above The Campaign for Cornell, Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: Far Above... The Campaign for Cornell, Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Item 2: Far Above The Campaign for Cornell, Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Item 3: Far Above The Campaign for Cornell, Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - ILR School, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Item 1: The MILR/UCD Semester in Dublin Program, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Institute for Workplace Studies, Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: Institute for Workplace Studies, Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Item 2: Institute for Workplace Studies, Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Item 3: Institute for Workplace Studies, Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Labor- Management Documentation Center, Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: Labor-Management Documentation Center, Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Item 2: Labor-Management Documentation Center, Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Item 3: Labor-Management Documentation Center, Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - MPS Program New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Item 1: MPS Program New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Shirley F. Harper Library Director's Conference Room, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Item 1: Shirley F. Harper Library Director's Conference Room, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Item 2: Shirley F. Harper Library Director's Conference Room, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Item 3: Shirley F. Harper Library Director's Conference Room, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Advance: ILR Alumni Magazine, 2014; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Item 1: Advance ILR Alumni Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
      By Cornell University ILR School. Spring 2014. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Advance ILR Alumni Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
      By Cornell University ILR School. Spring 2014. Copy 2. Item is in English.
    - Item 3: Advance ILR Alumni Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
      By Cornell University ILR School. Spring 2014. Copy 3. Item is in English.
    - Item 4: Advance ILR Alumni Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
      By Cornell University ILR School. Fall. Item is in English.
    - Item 5: Advance ILR Alumni Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
      By Cornell University ILR School. copy 2; Fall. Item is in English.
    - Item 6: Advance Ilr Alumni Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
      By Cornell University ILR School. copy 3; Fall. Item is in English.
  - Advanced Certificate in Performance Pay, Metrics and Practice Alignment, 2014-2015; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Item 1: New- Advanced Certificate in Performance Pay, Metrics and Practice Alignment, Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Item 2: New- Advanced Certificate in Performance Pay, Metrics and Practice Alignment, Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Item 3: New- Advanced Certificate in Performanc Pay, Metrics and Practice Alignment, Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - CAHRS Benefits, Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Item 1: CAHRS Cornell's Center for Advance Human Resource Studies, Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Item 2: CAHRS Cornell's Center for Advance Human Resource Studies, Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Item 3: CAHRS Cornell's Center for Advance Human Resource Studies, Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Customized Programs for Labor Unions, Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Item 1: Customized Programs for Labor Unions, Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Item 2: Customized Programs for Labor Unions, Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Item 3: Customized Programs for Labor Unions, Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Executive Master's Degree in Human Resource Management, 2013; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Item 1: Executive Master's Degree in Human Resource Management, Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Item 2: Executive Master's Degree in Human Resource Management, Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Groat and Alpern Awards, 2015; Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Item 1: Groat & Alpern Awards 2015, Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
      By Cornell University ILR School. invitations, RSVP cards, and pre-reception reservation cards. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Groat and Alpern Awards 2015, Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
      By Cornell University ILR School. invitations, RSVP cards, and pre-reception reservation cards; copy 2. Item is in English.
    - Item 3: Groat and Alpern Awards 2015, Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
      By Cornell University ILR School. invitations, RSVP cards, and pre-reception reservation cards; copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Healthcare Transformation Project, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Item 1: Healthcare Transformation Project, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Human Capital Development, 2014; Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Item 1: Human Capital Development Professional Programs, Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Item 2: Human Capital Development Professional Programs, Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Item 3: Human Capital Development Professional Programs, Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - ILR Conference Center, Publication (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Item 1: ILR Conference Center in King-Shaw Hall, Publication (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Item 2: ILR Conference Center in King-Shaw Hall, Publication (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Item 3: ILR Conference Center in King-Shaw Hall, Publication (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Institute for Compensation Studies, Publication (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Item 1: Advancing the World of Work: Institute for Compensation Studies, Publication (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Item 2: Advancing the World of Work: Institute for Compensation Studies, Publication (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Item 3: Advancing the World of Work: Institute for Compensation Studies, Publication (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - MPS Program: New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Item 1: MPS Program New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)